各位 又到了失物招领箱的
Okay, everyone. Time to dig it up
宝物发掘时间
what's in the Lost and Found box.
如果我的尊严在里面
If my dignity is in there,
帮我向它打个招呼
tell it I said "What up?"
这是我一个月中最喜欢的日子
This is my favourite day of the month.
天啊 我堕落得太快太深了
Oh God, I'm falling so far so fast.
没有这么夸张啦
You haven't fallen that far.
第一件是 发束
First item, a scrunchie
我需要这个 给我
I need that! Give me!
我堕落到极限 该停了
I think I hit my bottom.
好了 下一件
Okay, next item.
验孕棒
A pregnancy test.
那盒子是空的
That's empty.
看我干嘛 我有两分钟空档
What? I had two free minutes,
有孕验孕 没孕强身嘛
and you never know.
能不能快点
Can we move this along?
我年纪大了 得早点上床
I'm an old man, and I need to get to bed.
你是约了妹子"上床" 现在迟到了吧
You are late to meet woman for hot date.
还是你懂行
You know it.
一个钱包
A wallet and...
可惜没钱
no money.
看我干嘛 如果我怀孕了
What? If I was pregnant,
我得花钱去打孩子啊
I needed it for the baby.
最后一样 是连续六个月都有的
And finally for the sixth month in a row...
假发
The wig.
The wig!
阿憨 这次该你了
Han, it's your turn.
除了你 我们都戴过了
We have all put it on except you.
连我都戴过这玩意拍照了
If I had to take a picture in it,
你也得做同样的事情
you have to take a picture in it.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我可真是个风趣的老板啊
Man, I'm a fun boss.
不好意思 先生 我们打烊了
Oh, sorry, sir. We're closed.
我来看看是不是把假发忘在这了
I was just checking if I left my toupee here.
快点拍照
Take the picture quick.
我拿到了 拿到了
I got it. Here it is.
最新一期《玛莎生活杂志》
The new Martha Stewart Living.
我跑得超快 那个图书管理员说
I ran so fast, the librarian said,
"不许在图书馆乱跑" 我差点就回他
"Stop running in the library," and I almost said,
"我不是跑着玩 我是偷书"
"This is different. I'm stealing."
你为什么还每个月
Why are you still even looking
都看这本破杂志啊
through Martha Stewart living every month?
因为她可能会在里面提到我们啊
'Cause we might be mentioned in it.
玛莎说她没有忘记我们
Martha said she hadn't forgotten about us.
我妈当年也是这么说的
That's what my mother said,
最后老娘落得了在学校停车场
but I spent a whole day and night
等了整整一天一夜的下场
in that school parking lot.
不幸中的大幸是
Silver lining-
我现在还会唱TLC乐队那首《瀑布》的说唱部分
I still know the whole rap part to TLC's Waterfalls.
我还抱着我们会在书中出现的希望
Well, I'm still holding out hope we're in this,
虽然我已经连续两个月被伤透了心
even though I've been hurt two months in a row.
天啊 我是不是跟一个指点生活的专家
Oh, god, am I in an abusive relationship
在谈一场虐恋啊
with a lifestyle guru?
好吧 我们快快过一遍
Okay, let's get this over with.
"如何让他爱上你做的鲑鱼"
"How to make him love your salmon."
"如果让他爱上你的妊娠纹"
"How to make him love your stretch marks."
拜托 他就是不爱你嘛
Hey, he just doesn't love you.
全是达能酸奶广告 广告 广告
Activia ad, activia ad, activia ad.
我们知道啦 杰米·李
We get it, Jamie Lee.
你消化好排便畅
You poop lot.
"让你的烤箱有如大师般洁净"
"Get your oven Martha-clean,"
"麦克斯的什么小蛋糕"
"Max's something cupcakes"
桌布 桌布 桌布
Scarf, scarf, scarf.
慢着 麦克斯的小蛋糕
Wait, Max's cupcakes?
你刚是说"麦克斯的什么小蛋糕"吗
You just said, "Max's something cupcakes."
是吗
I did?
我的耳朵还真不习惯
Wow, my ears are so not used
听进我嘴里说出来的好话
to anything good coming out of my mouth.
这里这里 你看
There. There. Look.
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕
"Max's homemade cupcakes
是威廉斯堡必尝好滋味"
is a Williamsburg must-have."
这是什么 我的脸在干嘛
What's this? What's my face doing?
-你在笑啊 麦克斯 -不可能
- You're smiling, Max. - No way!
天啊 天啊 这是商品宣传
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. It's a blurb.
各位 《玛莎生活杂志》在帮我们做宣传
Everyone, we got a blurb In Martha Stewart Living.
能再给我来杯咖啡吗
Can I get some more coffee?
你疯啦
Are you insane?
大家好啊
Hey, everyone.
干嘛这么激动
What's the excitement?
是因为我来了吗
Is it 'cause I'm here?
苏菲 快看 《玛莎生活杂志》
Sophie, look, Max's homemade cupcakes
在帮"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"做宣传哦
got a blurb in Martha Stewart Living.
真有意思
Oh, that's funny,
因为《纽约公寓杂志》也在帮我做宣传
'cause I got a blurb in New York Apartment Life.
瞧 "苏菲的选择清洁公司
Look. "Sophie's choice cleaning service--
她们为了生活做牛做马 流血流汗"
they clean like their life depends on it."
那跟这个不一样啦
Well, that's not exactly the same.
当然不一样 瞧 我得到三个皮搋子
No, 'cause, look, I got three plungers.
没错 我本来不想吹嘘的啦
Yeah, but I didn't want to brag.
一定是安迪问我
That must be andy wondering
晚上要不要过去滚床单
if I'm coming over to have sex tonight.
我的人生还能再美好点吗
Could my life get any better?
天啊 还真能
Oh, my God. It could get better.
我们有十个蛋糕订单
There are, like, ten cupcake orders here.
生日派对 新生儿派对 割礼
Birthday, baby shower, bris.
我们可以接割礼吗
Can we do a bris?
当然 我做点玫瑰造型的包皮
Sure. I'll just make a little rosette foreskin
然后在外面写上
and write around the outside,
"恭喜你 20年后不会吓着女人了"
"Congratulations on not terrifying women in 20 years."
你好 安迪
Hey, Andy.
你好 糖果
Hi, candy.
你看到了吗
Did you see it?
你看了新一期的《玛莎生活杂志》了吗
Did you see the new Martha Stewart Living?
抱歉 没有
Oh, sorry, no.
我还没看完本期《魅力》跟《新娘》女性杂志呢
I still have to get through my Glamour and Modern Bride.
我有姐姐 所以知道那些杂志名不为过
And I had sisters, so I'm allowed to know those names.
"威廉斯堡必尝好滋味" 不错啊
"A Williamsburg must-have." Nice.
我一直觉得你也是
You know I feel the same way about you.
真会说话 不过除非上了报章杂志
Aw, cute, but it really doesn't mean anything
不然不算数
unless it's in a blurb.
我都等不及要拿给你看呢
I couldn't wait to show this to you.
真庆幸你还在这里加班整理存货
I'm so glad you were here late doing inventory.
是啊 说来也怪
Yeah, you know, it's the weirdest thing.
我唯一不知道去哪里的就是
The only thing I can't account for
一个猫王的糖果盒 麦克斯
is one missing Elvis Pez dispenser, Max.
我不知道你在说什么 但...
Um, I don't know what you're talking about, but...
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我们能回到宣传这个话题吗
Can we please get back to the blurb?
抱歉 你说得对
Sorry. You're right.
我应该更重视这件事
I should have made a bigger deal about it.
只是我有点被吓到了
It's just I've been a little freaked out.
这里今天发生了件大事
We had some big drama here today.
小糖果屋能发生什么"大事"
Drama in a candy store?
是不是被酸奶裹着的葡萄干终于意识到
Did the yogurt-covered craisins finally realize
自己是多么愚蠢 然后集体自杀了
how stupid they are and commit mass suicide?
不 不过说真的
No, but seriously they pulled some bodies
今晚他们从对面的施粥坊运出几具尸体
out of the closed-down soup kitchen across the way tonight.
所以现在完全不聊宣传这事了吗
So now we're completely off the blurb?
有些不明人士闯进去
Some guys broke in.
然后一堆人被乱枪打死
A bunch of people got shot.
显然是毒品交易谈不拢
Apparently, it was a drug deal gone wrong.
-天啊 太可怕了 -就是啊
- Oh, my God. That's horrible. - I know.
为什么毒品交易总是谈不拢呢
Why can't a drug deal ever go right?
听人说当时血肉横飞啊
Hey, they said it was a real bloodbath.
我要去看
I want to see it!
好吧 我得合上杂志了是吗
Oh, okay, so I'm closing the magazine then?
麦克斯 你不能进去
Max, you can't go in there.
那可是犯罪现场 有警察封锁带
It's a crime scene. There's police tape.
她会魔术吗
Is she magic?
我妈有个男友过去专门偷电子商店
One of my mom's boyfriends used to rob electronic stores.
有次作为生日礼物 他带了我去
He took me once for my birthday.
这附近应该有灯的开关啊
Hmm, there should be a light switch around here.
-天啊 -这太恶心了吧
- Oh, my God. - Oh, that's really gross.
这是我见过最棒的东西
That's the greatest thing I've ever seen!
帮我在这里拍张照片
Take a picture of me over here.
我终于有理由加入网上照片分享的行列了
I finally have a reason to join Instagram.
人们浏览照片时肯定会这样 "食物 食物
People are gonna be like, "Food, food,
猫 食物 指甲 指甲 谋杀啊"
cat, food, nails, nails, murder?"
伙计们 我得走了
Guys, I can't be in here.
我吃饭有肉汁都想吐了 更何况这个
I get queasy if the meat juice touches my peas.
这是你第一次见到血溅一墙吗
Is this your first blood splatter?
真是个温室花朵小公主啊
Jeez, someone's a princess.
天啊 这地方以后肯定没人敢租了
Man, they are never gonna be able to rent this place now.
我要回店里 往墙上浇点血
I'm gonna go over to my store and put blood on the walls
好讨麦克斯欢心
so Max will like it more.
麦克斯 看看四周
Max, look around.
你想的跟我的一样吗
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
对 枪手站在这里
Yup. The shooter stood here,
依墙上溅开的血迹分析
and, based on the blood splatter,
他个子不高 走路会一瘸一拐
he was short and walked with a limp.
他名叫迈德·道格[疯狗]
And his name was Mad Dog.
因为我希望他叫这个
'Cause I want that to be his name.
不 麦克斯
No, Max,
我们不是一直想拥有自己的店面吗
you know how we've always wanted our own shop?
就是这里了
This is it.
这里就是麦克斯自制小蛋糕的店址
This is Max's homemade cupcakes.
好吧 我懂了
Oh. Yeah, I see that.
还可以把我们的红色天鹅绒
And we can put our red velvets over there
摆那边的头骨碎渣旁
by the random skull fragments.
再说了 我们不是要把店开在曼哈顿吗
Besides, I thought our shop was gonna be in Manhattan.
曼哈顿已经落伍了
Manhattan's over.
现在威廉斯堡才是新的流行地
Williamsburg is the new hot area,
而且书上说我们是威廉斯堡必尝的美味
And besides Martha's blurb says we're a Williamsburg must-have,
所以我们必须租下这里
So we must have this space.
错 我们必须先弄得钱
No, we must have the money.
这地方起码得4千块一个月啊
I mean, this place has got to be, like, $4,000 a month.
那是过去 过去可能得一个月4千
Was. Was $4,000 a month.
那是悲剧发生前的价格
That was the pre-tragedy price.
一旦死过人 多少钱就是买家说了算
When people die, it's a buyer's market.
想在出过事的高档酒店住上一晚
You want to rent a room in that shining hotel now,
大概50块一晚就行了
It's, like, 50 bucks a night.
虽然我很想在一个发生过
Well, obviously I wanna start a business
连环射杀凶案的地方开店
in a place where there was a shooting spree.
而且如果想漆成红墙 这都半完工了
And, if we go with red, it's half painted.
但我们要去哪里弄这笔钱
But where are we gonna get the money?
玛莎的宣传就是我们银行里的钱
This blurb is our money in the bank.
真好 又多了一样我们没有的东西
Oh, yeah, that's another thing we don't have.
银行
A bank.
有些专门为了支持其他女性的
There are places set up by women
小本生意的而创立的机构
specifically to support other women's small businesses.
我说的是"女女融资"
I'm talking girl-on-girl financing.
名字真肉欲
That's hot.
但不管她们能借给咱们多少钱
But I don't care how much money they offer us.
我都不会出卖自己身体的
I'm not braiding anyone's hair.
但我们真的准备好了吗
But are we ready?
好吧 没错
Okay, yes.
这的确是一步险棋
This is a big leap of faith,
但有了宣传后 我们的订单也多了起来
but we're getting in lots of orders now thanks to the blurb.
而且最坏又能如何呢
And what's the worst thing that could happen?
比如墙上会是我们的脑浆
Um, maybe these could be our brains.
不 不会的
No, not gonna happen.
我们一定能大杀四方
We're gonna kill it.
我完全没有对任何
No disrespect to any spirits
还在苦苦寻求解脱的灵魂不敬
still trying to find their way into the light.
我会选好地方
I'll figure out a place,
明早一起来我们就去
and we'll go first thing in the morning.
打扮得像点生意人 少穿低领
Find something business-y to wear, less cleavage.
这些就是我的生意"本钱"
Oh, these are all business.
很好 我要去找安迪了
Great, I'm gonna go find Andy.
怎么说到房地产会让我想隔衣干"磨蹭"啊
What is it about real estate that makes you wanna dry hump?
麦克斯 我好兴奋啊
Max, I'm so excited.
我们要实现我们的梦想了
We're getting our dream.
看起来你想来个爱的抱抱
You look like you want a hug.
没错
I do.
晚安
Good night.
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
"Max's homemade cupcakes,"
轮到你了
You're up.
卡洛琳 你干嘛不接电话
Caroline, why didn't you pick up?
提早轮到我们了 而且我也不懂
They just called us early, and I don't know
该怎么填这表格
what to write on the paper.
我感觉像个白痴一样 胸也要被衣服闷死了
And I feel like an idiot, my boobs are suffocating,
而我唯一能找到的正装 是阿憨的夹克
and the only "business" thing I could find was Han's blazer.
穿起来身上好痒 而且口袋里有个纸条
It's itchy, and there's a piece of paper in the pocket
上面写着他名字
with his name on it.
他干嘛要写名条放口袋啊
Why would he have that?
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
"Max's homemade cupcakes,"
时间就是金钱哦
Time is money.
在
Um, here.
但我们预约的是20分钟后呢
But our appointment's not for another 20 minutes.
请就座
Have a seat.
这地方挺不错啊
Cool place.
女性的小本生意
Women's small businesses.
姐姐妹妹为了自己的前途而来这
Sisters doing it for themselves.
我是为了医疗福利而来这
Well, I'm doing it for the medical benefits.
-说吧 -现在就开始吗
- Go. - Oh, now?
我搭档人还没到呢
Before she gets here?
我这人不太懂做生意呢
Um, well, I'm not really much of a business person.
好一个生意贷款申请的开场白啊
Great way to start a business loan application.
快说
Go!
给你一分钟讲
You have a minute.
好吧 我... 我还剩多少时间
Okay, well, um, how much time do I have now?
不到一分钟
Slightly less than a minute.
我的生意伙伴
Okay, uh, my business partner
肯定能解释得比我好 但我尽量吧
could explain this better than me, but I'll try.
我们拥有个小蛋糕生意
We have a cupcake business.
我们在我室友的房里烤小蛋糕
And we bake cupcakes in my roommate's bedroom.
我听不见你说的
I can't hear you.
你要用写的 画的 或是用粘土捏给我看吗
You want to write it down, draw it, shape it in clay?
我本来也想多填一点
I would have filled this out more,
但那边那妞不让我抄她的
but that chick over there wouldn't let me cheat off her.
她不是那种女女互助型的妞啊
She's not a girl's girl, know what I mean?
非常"专业"
Very professional.
过去还贷历史
Under past loan repayment,
你填了 "还了我欠陶德的酒债"
you put, "Paid todd back all the beer money I owed."
这可是好事 他那人整天醉醺醺的
To be fair, he was drunk all the time.
我都没骗他说我还钱了呢
I could have just said I did.
给我的诚实加个分嘛
Points for honesty.
我再拿一份新的贷款申请表给你吧
Let's get you a new loan application.
才看到你的短信
Just got your message.
我第一次没早来就出事了
The one time I don't come early.
说到"来" 我刚体验了这辈子最棒的性高潮
Speaking of that, I just had the most amazing orgasm.
我跟安迪性生活是一直很美满啦
I mean, we've been having really great sex,
但今早 我爽得都停不下...
but this morning, I could not get enough of his--
要看他的预期增长比投资分析报告了
projected growth ratio investment analysis.
您好 卡洛琳·钱宁
Hello, Caroline Channing.
沃顿商学院09年毕业生
Wharton class of '09.
这是我们的商业计划书
That's our business proposal.
幸好在座各位都是女性
And I would be a little embarrassed about what just happened
不然刚才就更尴尬了
if I didn't know that we're all just girls here.
能快点弄完这事吗
Can we move this along?
我有堵塞马桶跟怀孕的狗等我回家弄呢
I got a busted toilet and a pregnant dog at home.
你干嘛不提醒我她在桌子下面
Why didn't you tell me she was under there?
是我不对 我没算到会听到一段
Oh, sorry, I wasn't expecting a monologue
"应召女郎的独白"
from confessions of a call girl.
恐怕我们无法贷款给你们
I'm afraid we're gonna have to deny the loan.
为什么 就因为她高潮到炸吗
Why? Because she had a good orgasm?
你们70年代的妞不是最爱"做"了吗
Isn't that what the '70s was about for you gals?
你们没有生意经验
You have no business history.
但那是我们的基本要求
And that's a requirement for us.
好吧 那恕我们不奉陪了
Well, I think we're done here.
我刚不就是这意思吗
Yeah. I just said that.
我还以为你们的主旨是
I thought you guys were about
支持女性的小本生意
supporting small women's business.
而这小女人的"小生意"今日连遭"撞击"
And this small woman's "bidness" needs support
不正需要你们的支持吗
after the pounding it took today.
麦克斯 走吧
Max, let's go.
我找到一家在新罕布什尔的银行
Okay, there's a bank in New Hampshire
他们什么资料都不会查
that doesn't check anything.
趁别人还没抢走咱们要的店面之前
And before someone else grabs our cupcake space,
我们赶紧上公车去一趟吧
I say we get on a bus and go up there.
他们不愿意给详细地址
They won't give out their exact address,
只说是在小商城里 有白城堡标识[速食店]
but I know they're in a mini mall with a white castle.
我有更好的提议
Better idea.
我上了分类广告网站
I went to Craigslist,
点了其他类
Clicked on "etc"
找到了各种赚钱的机会
and found all kinds of opportunities to make some cash.
我在强忍眼眶中悲哀的泪 你接着说
I'm fighting the instinct to weep, but keep going.
看到了一个闻香师工作
At first I thought I might call pit pig.
结果人家是要找人闻他腋下
He just wants his armpits smelled,
但貌似要闻个一千次左右
but that's, like, 1,000 sniffs.
牺牲颇大
Big commitment.
还有另一个怪人要找个貌美的截肢者
Or there's the weirdo looking for pretty amputees,
但感觉这活牺牲更大
but that feels like a bigger commitment.
所以 看这个吧
So, check it.
"寻求卵子捐赠者
"Egg donors needed.
酬劳一到两万"
Ten to twenty grand."
别想 我死也不卖我的卵子
No way, I could never sell my eggs.
你难道喜欢在心里老惦记着
I mean, wouldn't you hate to think
自己可能有个孩子在外面吗
you had a kid out there and not know it?
我早有了吧
I probably do.
我06年发明了能量酒精饮料混感冒糖浆奶昔
In 2006, I invented the Four Loko and robitussin smoothie.
我整年都在神志不清呢
It's pretty much a blackout year.
价钱合理 卖光所有卵子也行
Seriously, for the right price I'd sell 'em all.
真的吗
Really?
我是知道你一直都是女猛将
I mean, I know you've always been tough.
也听你说过
To hear you tell it,
你曾是地下婴儿搏击俱乐部的一员
you were part of an underground baby fight club.
但你难道没想过有天要当妈吗
But don't you wanna be a mom some day?
从古到今
In the history of the world,
举一个好妈妈的例子给我听听
give me one example of a really good mother.
这问题把我难住了
You're putting me on the spot.
我脑子里浮现的只有希拉里·达芙
All I can think of is Hilary Duff.
听我说 这事情很简单
Look, you're complicating this
是你感情用事 才这么复杂
with these things you call emotions.
无论你接不接受
Like it or not...
我就是个蛋鸡
I'm an egg farm.
而除了新罕布什尔的那地方 我们找不到人
Because we don't know one single person outside of New Hampshire
会愿意借我们这么多钱的
who can lend us that kind of money.
姑娘们 看看窗外
Yoo-hoo, girls, look out the window.
看上面 是我
Up here! It's me!
奥列格跟我想要两个小蛋糕
Oleg and I would like two cupcakes please.
要跟苏菲借钱 感觉好怪哦
I feel weird asking Sophie for money.
而且你知道她有那么多钱啊
And how do we even know she has any?
人家在波兰盖着梦想中的豪宅
Well, she's building her dream house in Poland
盖在旧死亡集中营跟五星酒店之间呢
between a former death camp and a New W.
她肯定超有钱
She's gotta be loaded.
况且苏菲是那种能理解我们梦想的女人
And Sophie's the kind of woman who understands our dreams.
请进
Come in.
我进门前就想到
That's exactly what I thought would be
门后会是这副光景了
on the other side of that door.
小甜甜奥列格 有客人来了
Oleg, sweetie, we have company.
我给你拿了屁屁枕头
I brought you an ass pillow.
在工作以外的地方能如此与你们相见 不好吗
Nice to see you like this outside of work, girls, no?
不好
No.
姑娘们 看到我的大"吊"物了吗
Girls, did you see my big hanging thing?
我们刚才是看到了
Yeah, we kinda just saw it.
不是 是我要装到豪宅里的大灯灯
No, I'm talking about my new ch-andelier for my lake house.
我都能想象你在灯下大喝喝美酒的场景呢
Yeah, I can totally see you drinking ch-ardonnay under it.
麦克斯 你真会搞笑
Oh, Max, you are so funny.
她的确是个大笑笑
She's a real ch-aracter.
哪有这个词
Yeah, that's not a word.
我们来送给你免费的小蛋糕
Okay, well, we just wanted to bring you
每次都是免费请你吃哦
some more cupcakes for free, per usual,
然后可能顺便跟你谈一个投资机会
and perhaps talk about a possible business venture.
抱歉了 姑娘们
Oh, sorry, girls.
我这辈子有两个规矩
I have two rules in life:
永远不喝吉普赛人也喝的同井水
Never drink from the same well as a gypsy
还有就是 永远不借钱给朋友
And never lend money to friends.
而麦克斯 你是我的朋友
And, Max, you are my friend.
没事 我们就问问 还是谢了
Okay, well, we were just checking, but thanks anyway.
苏菲 你听我们说说嘛
But, Sophie, just hear us out.
这是个千载难逢的机会
It's a wonderful opportunity,
我们会连本带利还给你
And we'll of course pay you back with interest.
好了 不送
Okay, buh-bye.
走吧 我们问过了
Let's go. We tried it.
现在到了下蛋的时间啦
Now it's---- time.
不许你靠卖器官组织赚钱
You are not harvesting your body for money.
这有什么啊
What's the big deal?
我房子的定金就是卖了两个肾赚来的
I sold two kidneys for a down payment on my house.
你骗人 起码得留一个才能活
Not true. You need at least one to live.
是吗 反正都不是我自己的
Oh, well, they weren't mine.
接下来要干嘛你应该心知肚明
Well, you know what we have to do.
咱们咕咕走人吧
Let's get the bok out of here.
你确定你愿意卖卵子赚钱吗
And you're sure you're okay with selling your eggs, right?
当然 这有什么所谓
Totally. What do I care?
反正我有好几百万个
I've got a million of 'em.
少几个卵子也挺好 能多装点啤酒
I'm happy to lose a few. More room for beer.
少留点卵子 多装点啤酒
Lose some eggs, more room for beer.
他们居然没拿来当标语
It's crazy that's not their slogan.
申请表上都问了什么问题啊
So what'd they ask you on the application?
老生常谈啊 收入 兴趣
You know, income, hobbies,
"有没有在非洲有过性行为"
"Did you ever have sex in Africa?"
我倒希望呢
I wish.
我最接近的一次 也就是一男的
The closest I ever got was a dude once
在非洲餐厅里把手伸到我裙子里非礼我
put his hand up my skirt in an ethiopian restaurant.
话说 来到这里以后
You know, now that we're here,
我其实觉得这地方也很美好呢
I think it's kind of wonderful that places like this exist
能帮助不孕的女人完成生育的梦想
to help women who can't have babies have babies.
如果有梅毒会被扣分吗
Hey, you think they take points off for syphilis?
麦克斯 你为我们梦想
Max, I think it's really noble
所做的牺牲真的很伟大
what you're doing to get our dream.
今天是个意义重大的日子
This is a very special day.
"衣原体感染"[性病]怎么拼啊
How do you spell "chlamydia"?
是C开头不是K
Well, no "K"s,
也可以不用画个小心装可爱
and I personally wouldn't heart the "I."
谢了
Oh, thanks.
那我兄弟猥亵儿童的往事需要写上吗
And do I gotta put here if my brother touched a kid?
麦克斯·布莱克
Max Black.
感谢您的抬爱
Thank you for your interest,
但很遗憾 我们无法接受您的卵子
but I'm afraid we're gonna have to pass.
为什么 我没在非洲有过性行为啊
Why? I didn't have sex in Africa.
是的 有给您加一分
Yes, I know, that was your one plus,
但家庭历史栏
But under "Family history,"
您填了"酗酒"与"秘密"
You put "Drinking" and "Secrets."
我是诚实回答啊
I was being honest.
您可能太诚实了 因为在"教育程度"栏
Yeah, maybe too honest, because under "Education",
您填写了"看益智节目重播"
you wrote, "Jeopardy reruns,"
而我们主要是想找大学毕业生
and we're really looking for college graduates.
靠 主持人 我选"精英主义"500块
Jeez, I'll take "Elitist" for 500, Alex.
抱歉 我们是想找
Sorry, we're looking for girls
常春藤盟校毕业
that come from Ivy league schools
而且有优良家庭背景的女孩
and have impressive family backgrounds.
虽然她的卵子不像我
Maybe her eggs didn't go to Wharton
有上过沃顿商学院 并以尖子生的身份毕业
and graduate at the top of their class like I did,
但你看看她
but just look at her.
谁不会想要这么坚强 貌美
who wouldn't want a baby with such strength, beauty,
胸器棒到能自我哺乳的女性的卵子呢
and a rack so great it could breast-feed itself?
你是沃顿毕业的吗
You went to Wharton?
常春藤毕业生我们付两万块哦
We pay $20,000 for Ivy league eggs.
哇 直接就抽血啦
Wow, we're taking blood already?
上过沃顿还真是让你领先普通人一大步啊
I guess going to Wharton does put you on the fast track.
只是当捐赠者的手续罢了
Just part of the process to become a donor.
我去拿点试管 马上回来
I'm gonna go get some vials, and I'll be right back.
你愿意这么做真是太酷了
It's so cool of you to do this.
能看出你是个怎样的人
It says a lot about you.
你知道什么能看出我是个怎样的人吗
You know what says a lot about me?
我能看出她橡皮管绑法错误[施打毒品需绑]
The fact that I know she tied you off wrong.
我很乐意来牺牲
I'm happy to do it.
为了让我们圆梦 这点代价不算什么
It's a small price to pay to make our dream come true.
我是来卖卵还债的
I'm doin' this to pay down some debt.
我买彩票搞得债台高筑
I'm real deep 'cause of powerball.
兄台 你是怎么通过筛选的
Whoa, dude, how did you get through?
我是哈佛毕业生
I went to Harvard.
我可是个数学天才啊
I'm like crazy-good at math.
麦克斯 她把我搞得都紧张了
Max, she's making me nervous.
拉上帘子
Close the curtain.
而且我还有点小不爽呢
And frankly, I'm a little resentful.
我都没考进哈佛
I didn't get into Harvard.
你确定你要干这事吗
Are you sure you're okay with this?
-你看起来有点神经紧张 -我没事啊
- 'cause you seem a little jumpy. - No, I'm fine.
他们就抽一点血而已嘛
They're just taking a little blood.
现在看起来
Or from the looks of it,
他们是想把我抽干
they're taking all of it.
之后敢给我烂饼干果汁你们就惨了[捐血赠食]
There better be a nice juice and a cookie after this.
请放轻松 抽八试管而已
Please relax. It's only eight vials.
他们会抽一大堆 以防有变种
They gotta take a lot to make sure they don't get a kid
或是畸形婴儿
with, like, another kid growing out of it.
麦克斯 我才感觉要来真的
Max, this all just got very real.
-牵住我的手 -你知道我不牵手的
- Hold my hand. - You know I don't hold hands.
你们这些死拉拉真是难搞
Oh, you lesbians are so high maintenance.
拜托嘛
Please?
我应该不会刚好卖掉我最棒的那颗卵吧
You don't think I'm gonna give away my best egg, right?
我可不想卖掉钢琴演奏家卵
I'm not gonna give away the concert pianist
而留下会入室抢劫
and get stuck with the guy who breaks into homes
并闻女性内衣物的变态卵吧
and smells women's underwear?
无论如何 两个孩子都很有激情啊
Well, either way, you got a kid with a passion.
你可以不必这么做的
But you don't have to do this.
为了我们的梦想 我可以的
No, I can do this. It's for our dream.
但你真的不必这么做
But you don't have to do this.
我可以 抽吧
I can do this. Put it in.
已经开抽了
It's already in.
我不能这么做
I can't do this.
我又不堕落 也不是农场动物
I'm not trashy, I'm not some farm animal.
我的天啊
Oh! Oh, my God!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我的老天啊
真的很对不起
I am so, so sorry!
你知道这里很适合开什么店吗
You know what would be cute here?
小蛋糕店
A cupcake store.
麦克斯 外面真冷啊
Hi, Max. Oh, it's chilly outside.
人人都冷得激凸啊
Nipples everywhere.
请坐 我马上过来
Have a seat. I'll be right over.
不用 我来的路上就先短信点餐了
Oh, that's okay. I texted my order in on the way.
宝贝 我收到你短信了
Hey baby, I got your text.
收到我的情欲俳句了吗
Did you get my erotic haiku?
收到
I did.
收到我与吸尘器的情欲艳照了吗
Did you get the picture I sent of me and the dustbuster?
没有啊
No, I didn't.
惨了 发到约基旭爷爷那里了
Oh, no, grandpa Yorgish!
你看
Look.
厄尔把宣传文章给表框了
Earl framed our blurb.
真的吗 他真有心
He did? That is so sweet.
怎么了
What?
我一直觉得这有机会挂到店里的墙上呢
I always saw it as bigger on the wall in our shop.
弄个店面的确是不错的主意
Look, the shop is an amazing idea,
这次的店面可能少了点缘分
And, if it's not that space right now,
下次还会有的嘛
it'll be another.
布鲁克林区到处都有疯狂屠杀 店面总会有的
I mean, there have to be mass murders all over Brooklyn, right?
我们够幸运就有了
If we're lucky.
就算到时候没成功
And, even if it didn't work out,
但也会是我这一生
it's still the closest I've ever come
最接近成功的一次 那也很好啊
to something great, and that's cool.
总有一天会找到愿意借钱给我们的疯子
And someday we'll find someone crazy enough to lend us money.
我说这个是因为 你都能说服我相信梦想
I say that because, if you can convince me to believe a dream,
天下没人能不被你说服了
You can get anyone.
上菜
Pickup.
苏菲 給 总共11块25
Here you go, Sophie. That's $11.25.
你们收支票的吧
Oh, you take a check, right?
这是2万块支票呢
This is for $20,000.
是吗 不是20块吗
Oh, is it? I thought it was for $20.
算了 你们收着吧
Oh, well. Keep it.
看你们是要拿去完成梦想
Maybe you could use it for your dream,
还是你要拿去除腿毛 随便啦
or to get your legs waxed, or something.
-苏菲 你是认真的吗 -是的
- Sophie, are you serious? - Yes.
苏菲 你这举动太太太棒了
Sophie, this is really, really amazing.
拜托哦 老娘不用你们礼赞
Oh, come on. I don't need a parade.
天天送小蛋糕来就是了
Just keep the cupcakes coming.
麦克斯 你知道这代表什么吗
Max, do you know what this means?
我们要成为威廉斯堡必尝好滋味了
We are going to be a Williamsburg must-have.
我们要实现梦想了
We're getting our dream.
看起来你想来个爱的抱抱
I feel like you want a hug.
没错
I do.